[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "What is Baby Yoda's real name",
        "answer": "Grogu"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "Where did Obi-Wan take Luke after his birth",
        "answer": "Tatooine"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "Who is Palpatine's granddaughter",
        "answer": "Rey"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "Who was Anakin Skywalker's Padawan",
        "answer": "Ahsoka Tano"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "What is Mando's real name from The Mandalorian",
        "answer": "Din Djarin"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "Who had the highest midi-chlorian count in Star Wars",
        "answer": "Anakin Skywalker"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "What year did the first Star Wars movie come out",
        "answer": "1977"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "Where is Jabba the Hutt's Palace located",
        "answer": "Tatooine"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "What's the name of Boba Fett's ship",
        "answer": "Slave I"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "Who are Kylo Ren's parents",
        "answer": "Han Solo and Princess Leia"
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "question": "Who killed Qui-Gon Jinn",
        "answer": "Darth Maul"
    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "question": "According to Yoda, there are always how many Sith Lords,,,no more, no less",
        "answer": "Two (Rule of Two)"
    },
    {
        "id": 13,
        "question": "What is the episode number of the very first Star Wars film",
        "answer": "IV"
    },
    {
        "id": 14,
        "question": "Who built C-3PO",
        "answer": "Anakin Skywalker"
    },
    {
        "id": 15,
        "question": "What is the name of Han Solo's ship",
        "answer": "The Millennium Falcon"
    },
    {
        "id": 16,
        "question": "Who acted as Queen Amidala's decoy",
        "answer": "Her handmaiden Sabé"
    },
    {
        "id": 17,
        "question": "What was Finn's stormtrooper number",
        "answer": "FN-2187"
    },
    {
        "id": 18,
        "question": "Where was Yoda's home in his final years",
        "answer": "Dagobah"
    },
    {
        "id": 19,
        "question": "Chancellor Palpatine was which Sith Lord",
        "answer": "Darth Sidious"
    },
    {
        "id": 20,
        "question": "Han Solo was frozen in what",
        "answer": "Carbonite"
    },
    {
        "id": 21,
        "question": "Who had Rey's parents taken and killed",
        "answer": "Palpatine"
    },
    {
        "id": 22,
        "question": "Luke lost which of his hands in a fight with Darth Vader",
        "answer": "His right hand"
    },
    {
        "id": 23,
        "question": "Finish this quote from The Mandalorian: This is the ___",
        "answer": "Way"
    },
    {
        "id": 24,
        "question": "Who killed Jabba",
        "answer": "Princess Leia"
    },
    {
        "id": 25,
        "question": "Who adopted Anakin and Padmé's daughter",
        "answer": "Bail Organa"
    },
    {
        "id": 26,
        "question": "On Tatooine, what name did Obi-Wan go by",
        "answer": "Ben"
    },
    {
        "id": 27,
        "question": "Anakin Skywalker grew up to be who",
        "answer": "Darth Vader"
    },
    {
        "id": 28,
        "question": "The Lion King's Mufasa and which Star Wars character were voiced by the same actor (James Earl Jones)",
        "answer": "Darth Vader"
    },
    {
        "id": 29,
        "question": "Per Yoda, what is the path to the dark side",
        "answer": "Fear"
    },
    {
        "id": 30,
        "question": "What species is Chewbacca",
        "answer": "Wookiee"
    },
    {
        "id": 31,
        "question": "Padmé was Queen of what",
        "answer": "Naboo"
    },
    {
        "id": 32,
        "question": "What is Kylo Ren's birth name",
        "answer": "Ben Solo"
    },
    {
        "id": 33,
        "question": "Who created Star Wars",
        "answer": "George Lucas"
    },
    {
        "id": 34,
        "question": "Who is Luke and Leia's father",
        "answer": "Darth Vader"
    },
    {
        "id": 35,
        "question": "Who told Anakin there is another Skywalker",
        "answer": "Yoda"
    },
    {
        "id": 36,
        "question": "Leia made who acting general",
        "answer": "Poe Dameron"
    },
    {
        "id": 37,
        "question": "Which character said, Help me, Obi-Wan Kenobi, You are my only hope",
        "answer": "Princess Leia"
    },
    {
        "id": 38,
        "question": "Bo-Katan wanted what from Moff Gideon in The Mandalorian",
        "answer": "The Darksaber"
    },
    {
        "id": 39,
        "question": "Which film was the final installment of the Skywalker Saga",
        "answer": "The Rise of Skywalker"
    },
    {
        "id": 40,
        "question": "Where was Baby Yoda when Order 66 was initiated",
        "answer": "Coruscant"
    },
    {
        "id": 41,
        "question": "What color was Mace Windu's lightsaber",
        "answer": "Purple"
    },
    {
        "id": 42,
        "question": "What color was Yoda's lightsaber",
        "answer": "Green"
    },
    {
        "id": 43,
        "question": "C-3PO is fluent in over how many forms of communication",
        "answer": "Over six million"
    },
    {
        "id": 44,
        "question": "What species is Jar Jar Binks",
        "answer": "Gungan"
    },
    {
        "id": 45,
        "question": "What is the name of Anakin's stepbrother",
        "answer": "Owen Lars"
    },
    {
        "id": 46,
        "question": "Who was Boba Fett's father",
        "answer": "Jango Fett"
    },
    {
        "id": 47,
        "question": "Who composed the soundtrack album to the 1977 film Star Wars",
        "answer": "John Williams"
    },
    {
        "id": 48,
        "question": "Who killed Mace Windu",
        "answer": "Darth Sidious"
    },
    {
        "id": 49,
        "question": "What is the name of the female member of the Jedi High Council who is of the same species as Yoda",
        "answer": "Yaddle"
    },
    {
        "id": 50,
        "question": "What was Galen Erso's nickname for his daughter",
        "answer": "Stardust"
    },
    {
        "id": 51,
        "question": "True or False, Boba Fett survived the Sarlacc pit",
        "answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "id": 52,
        "question": "How many episodes are in the Skywalker Saga",
        "answer": "Nine"
    },
    {
        "id": 53,
        "question": "Who is known for saying the line: I have spoken",
        "answer": "Kuiil"
    },
    {
        "id": 54,
        "question": "Who does Baby Yoda leave with in The Mandalorian Season 2 finale",
        "answer": "Luke Skywalker and R2-D2"
    },
    {
        "id": 55,
        "question": "Who played Princess Leia",
        "answer": "Carrie Fisher"
    }
]